wedding.net 2017-09-07

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy for personal information (hereinafter, the Policy) applies to all information that BRIDAL LLC (hereinafter, the Company) may obtain about the user while the latter uses any of the sites or services of the company (hereinafter, the Services). Use of the services, as well as registration on the websites of the Company, signifies unconditional agreement with this Policy and the conditions stated in it for processing one's personal information. In case of disagreement with these conditions, the user should refrain from using the Services.

In this Policy, «user's personal information» means personal information that the user provides voluntarily about himself/herself at registration (creating an account) or in the process of using the services, including the user's personal data.

Information required for providing the Services or for rendering other services is marked in a special way. Other information is provided by the user at his or her discretion.

The Company is not obliged to verify the accuracy of personal information provided by users and does not check their legal competence.

However, the Company assumes that the user is providing accurate and complete personal information and is keeping this information up to date.

### Personal Information

The Company collects and stores only the personal data that is necessary to provide the Services.

The Company may use a user's personal information for the following purposes:

  * Identifying parties and checking the accuracy of the data entered
  * Providing personalized services to a user
  * Communicating with the user, including sending notifications, requests, and information regarding use of the Services, rendering services, and processing requests and applications from the user
  * Improving the quality of the Services, their ease of use, and developing new services

The confidentiality of a user's personal information is maintained, except in cases where a user voluntarily provides information about himself or herself for access by the general public.

The company does not provide users' personal information to third parties.

A user can at any time change (update, supplement) the personal information already provided, or a part of it, in the personal section of the relevant service.

The management may at a user's request remove personal information provided by the user in a specific account. The user acknowledges and agrees that such a removal may render some services unusable.

### Protection of Users' Personal Information

The Company takes necessary organizational and technical measures to protect users' personal information.

The user must also take appropriate measures to protect his or her own personal information.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

The company has the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. The date of the most recent update is displayed. A revised Policy takes effect from the date of its posting, unless otherwise provided in the new version of the Policy.

The current version is always on a webpage at the address: <http://wedding.net/page/privacy/>

Revision date: 25 June 2016
